中文字幕由 硅谷字幕组 倾情奉献！
翻译：
徘徊的风，也许吧，Harry,
Pixel，L.E，Kwl，Hing，
噗次怪，tomato，喵喵
404nF找来了英文字幕文件和片源。还有其他成员的无私奉献。
送人玫瑰，手有余香。翻译美剧是提高英语的极佳途径！快来加入我们吧！
q群：718279851
Jian-Yang, are-- are you copying
Jian-Yang, 你准备抄袭
all those companies for the Chinese markets?
这些公司到中国市场吗？
-Oh, no. -♪ (MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
哦， 不是的
Are you suggesting that
你们觉得我们当中有人
someone in here is leaking info to Gavin Belson?
泄密给 Gavin Belson 吗？
Tell me about these... fridges.
告诉我关于这些冰箱的事情
(WHISPERING) It's a company secret.
商业机密
Do you want to save a fortune, or not?
你想省一大笔钱吗？想不想？
Well, yes.
好吧，当然想
In exchange, I need you to do something for me,
作为交换，我需要你为我做点事
with regard to the people who hacked your refrigerators.
至于黑了你们冰箱的人
I'm going to destroy their lives.
我会毁了他们的生活
Jared, do you think it's... time we hire a COO?
Jared，你觉得是时候雇一名COO了吗？
You're 20-30 pounds underweight.
你体重过轻了20到30磅
Don't worry about him.
别担心
We're gonna find you a much better COO.
我们会找到一个好得多的COO
You want the job?
你想要这份工作吗
-(GASPS, SOBS) -All right-- Ugh. All right.
好吧，啊，好吧
Okay, everybody, um, thanks for coming.
好吧，谢谢大家能够来
Uh, sorry about the venue.
呃，关于场地很抱歉
We had a minor security issue.
我们有一个小的安全问题
I didn't feel comfortable
我觉得不合适
hosting you guys at-- at our offices.
在办公室，集合大家
But, hey, at least out here,
但是，嘿，至少可以在这里
we don't run the risk
我们不冒这个险
of running into anyone from the tech industry.
碰到来自科技行业的任何人
(balls clack) Yeah, they're all so old.
对，他们年纪都太大了
But they look so happy. Yeah.
但是他们看起来好开心，对
It's weird.
好奇怪
I don't understand it either.
我也不明白
Anyway, I wanted you guys to meet,
不管怎样，我想让大家见个面
because despite being a very diverse
因为尽管你们是一个非常多样化
and talented group of young web developers--
有才华的年轻 Web 开发者团队
Goodscape, huh? Social coding platform.
Goodscape，恩？ 社交编程平台？
Tholio, analytics firm.
Tholio，分析公司
Plucky, music streaming.
Plucky，音乐流媒体
FirstSight, dating site.
FirstSight，交友网站
Gay dating site.
同性恋交友网站
Okay, technically, you're a dating site,
好吧，从技术上说，是交友网站
but specifically, a gay one.
但是具体地说，一个同性恋交友网站
Which is a subset, so I'm not wrong.
那是个子集，所以我没说错
Anyway, uh, despite all our differences,
无论如何，呃，尽管我们有很多分歧
we all have one thing in common, right?
但是我们有一个共同点，对吗？
A signed agreement with me
和我签署了一份协议
to build and launch your websites,
部署并启动你们的网站
not on the tired, bloated, old web,
不是在讨厌的，臃肿的，旧互联网上
but on the new Internet of the future.
而是在未来新一代互联网上
The Pipernet.
Pipernet
Which is why, from this day forward,
这就是你们来这的原因，从今天起
I'm going to be naming the eight of you...
我要称呼你们八个为
the OctoPipers.
八笛手。
Until something better, TBD.
直到想出一个更好的名字，再说吧。
So when can we tell people?
那什么时候我们才能公布出去呢？
Soon! Actually, very soon.
很快了！事实上，非常快。
Uh, next Tuesday, Gavin Belson is, uh...
嗯，下周二，Gavin Belson要，嗯……
launching his Box Three.
发布他的箱子3。
So, um, the day before,
所以，嗯，在那天之前，
we are going to announce our partnerships with you all,
我们将会公布我们之间的合作关系，
and beat him to the punch.
好好的打击他一下。
Shit. He's gonna be super pissed.
艹，他将会气死的。
Man: He's really gonna come after us.
他将会拼命报复我们的。
Yeah, he is, but fuck him.
是的，他会的，但操他的。
Not butt fuck him.
不是操他的屁股。
- Just...
- You don't have to explain
- 而是……
- 你不需要解释
that kinda stuff. I-I know what you mean.
那种事。我-我明白你的意思。
Yeah, I know. Look-- look.
对，我知道。看--看。
As long as we stick together,
只要我们团结在一起，
and support each other, we can crush him.
互相支持，我们可以粉碎他。
Because what we are doing is amazing, okay?
因为我们正在做的是很了不起的，对吧？
We are building the world's first truly open,
我们正在建设这个世界上第一个真正开放的，
truly free de-centralized Internet.
真正自由的分布式互联网。
And I tell you what, I got a sneak preview for you guys, okay?
而且我告诉你那啥，我搞了个预览让你们先偷偷看一下，好吧？
Because as of this morning,
因为就在这个上午，
messaging is live. What!
信息发送已经搞好了。什么！
Cool. Yeah.
酷。 是的
Really? So cool!
真的吗？太酷了！
So...
那么……
right now, I will send to you all
现在，我将给你们都发送
the very first message
第一个信息
ever to be sent on a de-centralized, peer-to-peer Internet.
之前从未在一个分布式、点对点互联网中发送过的。
Ready? (phone clicking)
准备好了？（电话嗒嗒声）
(sent message notification)
（发送信息提示音）
"Hit her." (phones dinging)
“打她。”（电话叮叮响）
I don't get it. Are you talking about me?
我不大明白。你是在说我吗？
I meant to say "Hi there."
我是想说“嗨，好吗？”
Well, it definitely says "Hit her."
嗯，但确实是“打她。”
I'll try it again. There's a new one. (phone clicking)
我再试一次。新的来了。（手机嗒嗒声）
There. "Hi there." (sent message notification)
来了。“嗨，好吗？”（发信息提示音）
"Hi there, Hitler." (phones ding)
“嗨，好吗，希特勒。”（电话叮叮声）
(whispers) Goddammit.
（低语）该死的。
Hey, Richard?
嗨，Richard？
You don't have any issue with us
你对我们没什么意见吧
being an exclusively gay site, do you?
关于我们是一个专门的同性恋网站这回事，对吧？
What? No!
啥？没有！
No, it's-- it's totally cool.
没有，那个--那个完全没问题。
Oh! Wait a minute, no, I don't mean you are anti-gay.
噢！等等，不，我不是说你反同。
I mean the opposite. Like, are you worried
我的意思是相反的，比如，你是担心
that we're excluding straight people?
我们排斥非同性恋
Oh. I just remember you said,
噢。我刚想起你说的，
you want your new Internet to be open for everybody,
你要你的新互联网对所有人开放，
and, you know, I just want to make sure we're jibing with your vision.
而，你知道，我只是希望保证我们和你的设想一致。
Deedee, we are psyched to have you aboard.
Deedee，我们非常高兴有你们加入。
Exclude all the straight people you want. (chuckles)
尽情的排斥你想要排的所有非同吧。（笑）
You sure? Yep.
你确定？ 是的。
Because we're not snobs about it. (chuckles)
因为我们对那个并不是非得坚持不可哦。（笑）
I mean, between you and me,
我的意思是，只是我们两个说说，
I'm dreadfully boring.
我真的无聊死了（很厌烦了）。
I might as well be straight myself.
我都有点想把自己改成非同性恋了。
I've been with the same man for seven years.
我和同一个男人在一起7年了。
I go to church every Sunday.
我每天周日都去教堂。
Look, it-- it's all good.
看，那-那都很好。
FirstSight is a gay dating site.
“第一眼”是一个同性恋约会网站。
And-- and I will sing it from the rooftops.
而且--而且我愿意站在屋顶上为它歌颂。
Alright, well, thank you, Richard.
好的，好，谢谢你，Richard。
I think this is gonna be great.
我想这将会很棒的。
Cool.
酷。
Yeah. Okay.
好。好的。
Don't be weird. I didn't know what we'd be doing.
别感到怪异。  我不知道我们要这样。
♪ ♪
Richard: So...
Richard：那个…
everybody is very psyched.
所有人都非常兴奋。
You know who else is psyched? I'll give you a hint.
你知道还有谁很兴奋吗？我给你个提示。
They have four thumbs, and they are these two guys.
他们有四个大拇指，并且他们就是这两人。
I am very excited. I am giddy!
我非常兴奋。 我兴奋晕了！
Okay, what-- what happened?
好的，发--发生什么事了？
We found the mole.
我们找到内奸了。
What? Yeah.
什么？是的。
Who? How?
谁？怎么找到的？
Good old-fashioned police work.
通过优秀的传统的侦察工作。
I skimmed through all 40,000 of the staff's outgoing emails.
我浏览了员工发出去的所有4万份邮件。
- Yeah?
- And in addition to learning
- 是吗？
- 然后除了发现
that we need to revise the office dating policy,
我们需要修改我们的办公室内约会规定，
because it is, essentially, the Olympic Village out there,
因为确实需要，本质上，就像个奥林匹克村（运动员们可是很淫乱的），
I learned that someone has been sending
我发现有人发了
a number of encrypted messages
一定数量的加密信息
but using Gilfoyle's purloined NSA tools--
但，使用Gilfoyle的国家安全局盗窃工具--
I can't hold this smile forever, Jared. Get to the good stuff.
我这微笑没办法永远保持下去，Jared。说重点吧。
One of our coders has been sending info
我们其中一个码工一直在发信息
straight to Hooli High Command.
直接去到Hooli总部高层。
Richard: Wow.
Richard: 哇呜。
How the fuck did the mole get all this information?
那内奸操他妈的是怎么搞到所有这些信息的？
By exploiting our most glaring weakness.
通过利用我们最光彩照人的缺陷。
(off-key) ♪ You were working as a waitress ♪
♪ 你在做一个女服务员的工作 ♪
♪ In a cocktail bar ♪
♪ 在一个鸡尾酒吧 ♪
♪ When I met Jeff ♪
♪ 当我遇见Jeff ♪
(theme music plays)
（主题音乐播放
No, no, no. You guys have it all wrong.
不，不，不。你们这帮家伙们都错了。
Okay? There's no way Jeff is the mole.
好吧？没有可能Jeff是那个内奸。
Okay? It's not Jeff.
好吧？不是Jeff。
(nail gun discharges) Right, Jeff?
（钉枪声）对吧，Jeff？
(clank)
（叮当声）
Jeff?
What about Dave & Buster's, Jeff?
还记得我们在Dave & Buster打机的时候吗？
（Dave & Buster是一个可以玩街机的地方）
What about that time I got a bullseye in Skee-Ball
那次我在Skee-Ball里直接命中目标
and yelled out, "Bazinga!"
大声喊道：“全中！”
And you said, "Okay."
你还说：“好的”
You can't fake enthusiasm like that.
你那种热情不可能是装出来的。
Well, I did.
我是装的
(nail gun discharges) Jared: You Judas.
（钉枪声）Jared：你这个犹大。
You cow-handed poltroon!
吃里扒外的家伙
We-- We thought you were a Stallion!
我们--我们视你为种马！
You're no Stallion. (nail gun discharges)
你不是种马了。（钉枪声）
What is it with you guys and stallions?
你们这些家伙干嘛老说种马种马的？
What's with you being a rat fuck?
你干嘛要做一个操他妈的叛徒？
You signed a very aggressive Non-Disclosure Agreement...
你签了一个非常严格的保密协议。。。
(nail gun discharges) which you are in breach of.
（钉枪声）然而你违反了它
(nail gun continues) Which means, we can fire you, obviously,
（又是钉枪声）这意味着，我们可以炒你鱿鱼，很显然，
and then have you arrested, and thrown in jail.
然后让你被逮捕，扔进监狱
But Gavin would then know we are on to you,
但是这样就会被Gavin知道我们识破了你的卧底身份，
so here's the deal.
所以，我们做个交易吧
You're gonna come into the office every day,
你每天都要来上班
and sit down at your fucking workstation,
呆在你那该死的工作台。
and pretend like nothing's wrong.
假装什么都没发生
(sighs) Fine.
（叹气）好吧。
(discharges)
（发射）
Uh, that was mine.
啊，那可是我的电脑
Bummer.
意外
"The irony is, the Internet, which we all use
“讽刺的是，互联网，我们都用来
to search for billions of things,
搜索亿万信息的东西，
"has itself long been searching for something.
它自己也一直在寻找某些东西。
And here it is."
而那东西就在这。”
Okay, then I turn and gesture.
Okay，说完我就会转身去揭晓
(serene music playing)
"The Box Three.
箱子3
Signature Edition."
签名版”
Then I come back to the podium.
然后我返回到台前
"I put my name on this,
我把我的名字放这上面，
"because I personally stand behind
因为我个人全力推荐
"the new SAS slash SSD slash NVMe drive bays,
新的SAS-SSD-NVMe硬盘组，
"the 24-core processors.
24核处理器
"I stand behind the ECC DDR4 SD-RAM LR-DIMMs
我全力推荐ECC DDR4 SD-RAM LR-DIMMs
"and their exceptional reliability.
和他们异常的可靠性。
Will you stand with me?"
你们愿意与我站在一起吗？
(applause)
（鼓掌）
(sets bottle down) (sighs)
（放下瓶子）（叹气）
About the spotlight, should it be wider?
关于聚光灯，难道不该再大一点吗？
I had the same thought. As did I.
我也是这么想的。我也是
I can speak with the technical team. Please.
我可以和技术人员说一下。  请说一下吧。
Any word from our mole at Pied Piper?
我们在花笛手的卧底有什么消息吗？
I'm confident that if there were anything to report,
我相信只要有任何需要报告的，
we'd have heard about it by now, sir.
我们现在就已经听到了，先生。
Alright!
好！
I'm off to Jackson Hole for a couple of days to clear my mind,
我要离开，去Jackson Hole几天清一清我的思绪，
and center myself.
然后回归自我。
I'll be off the grid. Not to be disturbed for any reason.
我将屏蔽所有联系渠道。任何原因都不要打扰我。
Understood? Scott: Absolutely.
明白吗？  Scott：完全明白。
Is there anything else you'd like us to take care of? Oh.
你有其他什么事需要我们处理一下的吗？噢。
The bear is sticky with honey.
小熊瓶子粘了蜜有点黏黏的。（请看7分29秒）
See ya soon.
再见。
"The bear is sticky with honey."
（直译）“那熊粘着蜂蜜。”
What does he mean by that?
他那是什么意思？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Hello, Stallions.
好啊，种马们。
You continue to be the best of the best.
你们保持最棒中的最棒。
I commend you.
我赞扬你们。
And then there's you.
然后还有你。
The anti-Stallion.
反种马。
Move your hand off your fucking mouse, now.
把你的手从操他妈的鼠标上挪开，马上。
And I was going to take you to see BattleBots live with me,
而我本来打算带你去看机器人大战现场比赛，
but no longer... "friend."
但不带你去了…… “朋友。”
Now who looks stupid?
现在谁看起来很傻？
♪ ♪
Yeah, so, um...
是的，所以，嗯……
our new developers just agreed to our terms,
我们新的开发者刚同意了我们的条款，
Richard (on phone): and are now officially on board.
Richard（电话中）：并现在正式加入了。
Richard is a master at getting consent.
Richard获得同意的技巧简直是大师级的。
That's great news, guys.
那真是好消息，伙计们。
Eight new partners.
8个新的合作者。
Yeah! Actually, we're calling them the OctoPipers.
是的！事实上，我们给他们取名叫八笛手。
Uh, until a better name comes along.
嗯，直到想出一个更好的名字。
Just wanted to give that one its day in court.
只是想要那个（名）有被评选的机会。
Well, we have some more good news for you, Richard.
好的，我们有更多的好消息给你，Richard。
You remember last year,
你记得去年，
Laurie and I funded K-Hole Games?
Laurie 和我投资了K-洞游戏吧？
Largest independent gaming company in the Valley?
谷中最大的独立游戏公司？
Uh, yeah, of course!
嗯，是的，当然！
Um, actually, now that you-- you bring them up,
嗯，事实上，现在你-你提起他们起来，
I-I didn't want to be too forward,
我-我不想太超前，
but I was hoping that one day,
但我正希望有一天，
we could talk to them about joining our 'net.
我们能跟他们谈谈关于加入我们的网络的事。
Well, what if I told you that day is today?
嗯，如果我告诉你那一天就是今天呢？
What?
什么？
In addition to being business associates,
除了业务来往以外，
the CEO and I take medically prescribed
那个CEO和我还一起吃医用的
and supervised MDMA together.
受监管的摇头丸（MDMA，兴奋剂）。
I'm taking it for severe post-partum depression.
我吃那个是因为严重的产后抑郁。
I do not know why he is taking it.
我不知道他为啥要吃。
Regardless, when I saw him yesterday,
不管怎样，当我昨天见他的时候，
he was quite euphoric about speaking to you regarding a deal.
他非常兴奋的想和你谈谈关于达成协议的事。
K-Hole? The creators of the game
K-洞？那游戏的创作者
"Undead Sex Offender"? They're-- they're huge.
“未死的性犯罪者”？他们--他们非常大。
Yeah! Yeah, partnering with a company of that size this early
是的！是的，这么早就和那种规模的公司合作
would put us months ahead.
可以让我们提前好多个月。
This is not a done deal.
这个还没有最终达成协议呢。
K-Hole is protective of its brand.
K-洞对它的牌子可是很重视的。
They will want to speak to you
他们想要和你谈谈
regarding who else you are dealing with.
关于你还和谁有业务关系。
Okay, right, well, um...
好的，对，好的，嗯……
why don't I just bring the OctoPipers?
我就说说八笛手怎么样？
New name to come, though it's pretty popular around here.
会有新名字的，虽然那名字在这儿挺受欢迎的。
Uh, they can talk to K-Hole.
嗯，他们可以和K-洞谈谈。
Tell them why they joined.
告诉他们为什么他们要加入。
Allowing you to speak less?
可以让你少说点话？
Good strategy. Alright.
很好的策略。好的。
K-Hole will be expecting you this afternoon.
K-洞将会在这个下午等着你去。
Knock 'em dead, Richard.
好好干吧，Richard。
Whatever you are doing, stop it now.
无论你正在干啥，现在就停下来。
Um, yeah. We're just... high-fiving.
嗯，好的。我们只是在……击掌。
Bye.
再见。
K-Hole. I can't believe it!
K-洞。我真不敢相信！
I'm bursting. I'm bursting!
我高兴爆了。我高兴爆了！
Um, here, I printed driving directions.
嗯，这儿，我打印了驾驶的路线指引。
Oh, it's okay, I got my phone.
哦，不用了，我带了手机
Well, I have marked available bathrooms along the route.
嗯，我在路上标注了可用的洗手间。
(hip hop music playing)
（hip hop音乐正在播放）
Okay, here we go.
好了，事儿来了。
Richard, you never return my calls.
Richard，你一直不回我电话。
You mean the hundreds of voicemails you've left
你是指你所留的几百个电话留言
where you just called me a terrible CEO with no dick?
那些你只是称我为没种的糟糕的CEO的话吗？
Yes! You're talking to other companies.
是的！你正在和其他公司谈生意。
(shushes) That is not public information.
（嘘---）那是还没公开的消息。
Jian-Yang: I'm a part owner in Pied Piper.
简阳：我是花笛手的部分拥有者。
You need to make a deal with my companies.
你需要和我的公司做笔生意。
You mean your incubator's spurious knock-offs
你是指你的孵化器的伪造仿冒
of legitimate American businesses?
美国原装企业的生意吗？
"New Expedia," "New Snapchat," "New Zillow"?
“新亿客行，”“新阅后即焚，”“新Zillow”？
But they're for Chinese market.
但他们是为中国市场而建的。
It's a very sophisticated strategy.
那是一个非常成熟的策略。
Okay, look, taking existing companies
好吧，看看，拿已经存在的公司
and just calling them "new" isn't sophisticated. That's theft.
然后加个“新”字不是成熟。那是剽窃。
You make a new Internet.
你做一个新的互联网。
(stammering)
(口吃的）
That is different.
那是不一样的。
I-- Look, we're not gonna make any deals
我——看，我们不会做任何生意
with any of your companies, okay?
和你任何一家公司，好吧？
(phone vibrates)
（手机振动）
Don't pick up.
不要接。
Richard, hello.
Richard，你好。
It's Jian-Yang.
我是简阳。
You are a shitty CEO.
你是一个狗屎CEO。
As long as I own 10% of Pied Piper,
只要我还持有魔笛手10%的股份
I will make chaos.
我就会给你捣乱的。
Okay.
好吧
I thought you hated that car.
我以为你讨厌这车
Aviato car smells like a dead pig.
Aviato的车臭死了，像头死猪
You're aware that Russ Hanneman urinated in that car, no?
Russ Hanneman往里面撒过尿, 你不知道？
This car?
这辆车？
Mm-hmm.
嗯
Uh...
呃...
are you just gonna leave it here? Yes.
你就打算就把它留在这儿? 是的。
Well...
好吧……
looks like I have a reason to find
看来我有理由去找
Pied Piper's official towing company.
花笛手的官方拖车公司了。
I'm gonna get some bids.
我会拿到好几家报价的。
Yeah, while you're at it,
是啊， 你在找的时候
see if you can find someone to bash that guy's face in.
能不能找人把那家伙修理一下
Uh, I-I can do some research.
额，我我可以找找看
(phone vibrates)
(手机振动)
Maybe turn your phone off during the meeting.
也许开会时你把手机关了吧
(yelling) You're a shitty CEO!
（大喊） 你是个狗屎CEO！
(screaming) (gunfire)
（尖叫） (枪声)
(violent noises continue)
(持续的暴力声响)
Richard: Thanks again, Colin, for having us.
Richard: 再次感谢，Colin, 让我们过来。
Uh, the fact that a company like yours
嗯，贵公司如日中天，如此牛气
with such a pristine reputation it sitting down with us
却还愿意坐下来和我们合作
is, honestly, incredibly flattering.
实在是让我们受宠若惊
It's cool.
还好了。
(man shouting in game) Ooh, wow.
(游戏中有人大喊) 呕，哇
That'll be a closed casket. Yeah.
那个可以装进棺材了。  是的。
Alright, well, we thought the best way
好吧， 我们觉得
to introduce the Pipernet
推出魔笛手网络的最佳方式
would be through the eight developers
得通过这八位开发者来完成
that have already signed on.
他们也都同意加入了
Who we are calling the OctoPipers.
我还给他们取了个名字: 八笛手
That's dumb.
逊毙了
Um, anyway, let's introduce you to the group.
不管怎样， 我先来介绍一下大家
Um, we've got a great analytics tool
这位是前谷歌大神
by a former Google guru.
做了个很棒的分析工具
Wish I'd have thought of that one. Cool.
真希望那是我想出来的。 酷。
Uh, music streaming with an AI taste predictor
还有内嵌人工智能预测器的音乐流媒体
that is off the charts.
那是超乎想象的。
Good space.
不错
Yes, and this handsome devil over here,
而这位帅到爆的小伙
is creating a very promising gay dating site.
正在搭建一个非常有前途的同性恋约会网站
That's cool. Yeah, but don't worry, he's not snobby about it.
很好。	别担心， 他也不是很坚持非得做这个。
He's actually pretty boring.
他实际上挺无聊的。
I don't mean that as an insult. Those are his words.
我不是侮辱他啊， 这都他自个儿说的。
Long-term relationship. Doesn't smoke, doesn't drink.
有长期的基友伴侣， 烟酒不沾
And him and his man go to church every Sunday.
而且他和他的男人每周日都去教堂
So...
所以....
loves Bible studies, right?
酷爱研习圣经，对吧 ?
Just a straight-up boring, ordinary guy,
就是一个超级无聊的普通人
but obviously not straight.
不过明显不是直男
Very gay, and also a Christian, right?
非常地弯， 还信教，对吧?
Richard: Okay, so, that went well.
Richard: 事情谈得还不错
It started out a little weird, but things really picked up-- Why did you do that?
刚开始有点别扭， 不过马上就进入正轨了 -- 你干嘛那么做 ?
Why did you say that? Say what?
你干嘛说那个 ？ 说啥了?
Richard, you just told a room full of tech people
Richard, 你跟满屋子的一群码农说什么
that I'm a (whispers) Christian.
说我(压低声音)信教
Oh.
欧
Okay, but-- but you are, aren't you?
好吧， 可是你不信教吗？
(whispers) Yes, but I told you that in confidence.
(窃窃私语) 我信教， 但这是我跟你私下说的。
I said "between you and me."
我说了“你知我知”
I'm not openly Christian.
公开场合我可不说信教
(sighs) Thanks a lot, man.
(叹气) 我真是谢谢你了， 兄弟
You just outed me.
你可把我给出卖了。
Oh, I'm sorry, Deedee. I didn't--
真不好意思， Deedee, 我真不知道--
Okay, um, should we hug?
好啦，我们要不抱一抱 ？
I can not make it weird this time.
这回我不会尴尬了。
I'm-- I'm sorry, Richard.
我--我很抱歉，Richard
You know that my default position
你知道不管你做什么
is blind support of whatever you do, but...
我都会无条件地挺你， 可是这回...
this was not your best moment.
你状态不行啊
Guys, it can't be that big of a deal, right?
兄弟们， 这有啥大不了的 ？
Why should it be?
为啥这是个事？
America loves Christians.
老美爱死基督徒了
Muslims are the enemy.
穆斯林才是敌人。
Well, that's true in most of America,
美国大部分地方是这样的
but not in Silicon Valley, sadly.
不幸的是， 硅谷除外
"Sadly"?  You can be openly polyamorous.
“不幸” ? 你可以和多人保持公开的情侣关系。
And people here will call you brave.
而这儿的人会说你有勇气。
You can put micro-doses of LSD in your cereal,
你在麦片里加点迷幻药
and-- and people will call you a pioneer.
大家会把你当做先锋
But the one thing you cannot be is a Christian.
但是你一定不能是基督教徒
I find their theology to be illegitimate,
我发现他们的神学是不合理的
and it's clear that they are the source
很明显
of the majority of the world's problems.
他们是世界上大多数问题的根源
But, fuck, Richard, even I wouldn't just...
但是，操，Richard，即使是我也不会
out a Christian like that.
像那样将一个基督徒公布出来。
Yeah, it was kinda fucked up.
是啊，那样也太糟了。
Cool man, thanks.
好的老兄，谢谢。
(softly) Hey, I thought he wasn't supposed to chime in.
（轻声的）嘿，我觉得他不应该插嘴啊
Yeah, he's not, but...
是的，他是不应该，但是。。
based on its merits, I'll allow that one.
对于他的观点，我表示赞同。
Guys, (stammers) come on.
你们不是吧
It can't be that bad.
情况不会那么坏吧
Richard!
Richard
What the fuck did you do over there?
你他妈的在那里做什么？
So I just got off the phone with Colin over at K-Hole,
我刚刚和K-Hole的Colin通了电话，
and while he loves your tech,
得知他们虽然很喜欢你的技术
he's considering blowing up the deal.
但他们正在考虑取消这次交易
What?
什么？
Just because one of my CEOs is Christian?
就因为我们其中一个CEO是基督徒？
It freaks people out in the Valley!
在谷中这吓死人们了！
Okay, so what do you want me to do, Monica?
好吧，那你要我怎么办呢，Monica？
You want me to drop Deedee just because he's Christian?
你要我因为Deedee是基督徒就抛弃他吗？
The company's not Christian. It's gay...
那公司不是基督徒。是同性恋…
which is fine, right?
所以没关系，对吧？
Yeah! No, that-- that plays great.
是的！不，那--那个很好。
Look, cutting all ties to Deedee and FirstSight
看，砍断与Deedee和“第一眼”的所有联系
will definitely send a strong message to Colin.
将会告诉Colin一个强烈的信息。
And it might be the only way.
而那可能是唯一的办法。
Like killing somebody to prove you're not a narc,
就像杀一个人以证明你不是卧底警察一样，
or showing a john your genitals
或者向一个嫖客裸露你的生殖器
to prove you're a legitimate male prostitute
以证明你是一个真的男妓
and not an undercover cop.
而不是一个卧底警察。
What? Because cops aren't allowed to do that.
啥？ 因为警察不准那样做。
And worst case scenario,
而最糟的情况是，
the john walks off with a free peek. (phone vibrating)
那嫖客看完就走了也没给钱。（手机振动）
Oh, that's the towing company. Excuse me.
噢，那是拖车公司。不好意思。
(groans) Forget it.
（叹息）算了。
Monica, I'm not doing it.
Monica，我不会那样做的。
I mean, I'm not dropping him.
我是说，我不会抛弃他的。
Alright. Fine.
好。没事。
Fine. I-I will call Colin,
好的。我-我将会打电话给Colin，
and try and smooth things over for you,
然后尝试为你把事情缓和一下，
but you need to handle Deedee.
但你得搞好Deedee那边。
Okay, apologize for outing him, of course,
好吧，为公布他的身份而道歉，当然，
but you need to make sure he keeps quiet about this.
但你得保证他对这个保持沉默。
Alright, 'cause it's not just about losing K-Hole,
好的，因为那不只是关于丢掉了K-洞，
it's way worse than that.
比那个糟糕多了。
Let's put it this way.
让我们这么说吧。
Would you want to go from being a rock band
你想从一个摇滚乐队
to being... (whispers) a Christian rock band?
变成……（小声说）一个基督徒摇滚乐队吗？
Oh, shit.
噢，操。
"The bear is sticky with honey."
“熊粘着蜂蜜。”
Those were his exact words.
那是他原本的话。
But what does that mean?
但那是什么意思呢？
Well, Gavin speaks in parables.
嗯，Gavin说的是比喻吧。
I think what Gavin is saying is...
我想Gavin想说的是……
"consider the bear."
“考虑一下那熊。”
And all this pizazz is like the honey.
而所有的能量则像是蜂蜜。
And it's become too sticky.
然而它变得太粘糊了。
There's too much of it. It's all over him.
过犹不及。对他来说太多了。
Incorrect. No, see, the whole launch is the bear,
不对。不，看，整个发布会就像一只熊，
and the honey is the pizazz.
而蜂蜜就是能量。
The bear needs more pizazz.
那熊需要多一些能量。
The bear is ravenous for pizazz.
那熊证渴望着能量。
You don't speak for Gavin.
你不能代表Gavin。
I don't need to. This is the word of Gavin.
我不需要。这就是Gavin说的。
Alright, forget it.
好吧，算了。
You do it your way, I'll do it mine. Okay, fine.
你按你的方法做，我按我的。     好的，好。
- Gonna show you.
- Okay, follow me.
- Make it clear for all of you.
- 做给你看看。
- 好的，听我说。
- 让你们所有人都一清二楚。
Jared: Well, congratulations on becoming
Jared: 嗯，恭喜成为
Pied Piper's official towing company.
花笛手的官方拖车公司。
Uh-huh, yeah, great.
嗯-哈，是的，太好了。
So should I bill this to you,
那么我该把这个记在你帐上，
or is Mr. Bighetti gonna take care of it?
还是Bighetti先生会搞定？
"Bighetti"? It's registered under his name.
"Bighetti"?  这登记在他的名下
I'm sorry. Can I...?
对不起。我可以……？
♪ ♪
Richard: Anyway, it was a mistake.
Richard: 不管怎样，那是个错误。
I'm sorry I outed you.
对不起公布了你的身份。
I just wish we could go back to normal.
我只是希望我们能回到平常的状态。
You know, just like, how things were.
你懂的，就像，事情之前的样子。
A CEO and a gay CEO.
一个CEO和一个同性恋CEO。
I don't even know what normal is anymore, Richard.
我已经不知道什么是正常的了，Richard。
It's been such a crazy 24 hours, you know?
那24小时简直太疯狂了，你明白吗？
Gossip travels so fast in the Valley.
流言蜚语在硅谷传播得如此之快。
I'll be lucky if my parents ever talk to me again.
如果我的父母能再跟我说话，我就算是幸运的。
Your parents aren't Christian?
你的父母不是基督徒？
I'm from Palo Alto.
我来自帕洛阿尔托。
You know, my dad says my lifestyle makes him sick.
你懂的，我爸爸说我的生活方式让他恶心。
He just wants his gay son back.
他只是想要回他的同性恋儿子。
And he's okay with the gay part?
那他对同性恋的部分没意见吗?
He's gay. Oh.
他就是同性恋。欧。
But the crazy part is,
但是疯狂的地方是，
when I finally got home and I got in bed,
当我终于回到家，躺在床上的时候，
I had the soundest sleep I've had in years.
这是我几年来睡的最好的一次。
Exhaustion. No! Relief, Richard.
疲惫。      不！解脱，Richard。
I'm out, okay?
我终于把身份公布了，好吗？
My nightmare's over.
我的噩梦结束了。
I don't ever have to go back in the closet again,
我再也不用回到柜里了，
and I've got you to thank for it.
我要感谢你。
Check it out.
看。
Oh, oh, oh.
欧，欧，欧。
You like it?
你喜欢吗?
It's good. I guess... maybe it's just a little busy?
挺好的。我猜……或许有一点忙？
Like, um, there's one word too many.
就像，嗯，有一个词显得太多了。
One word? Well, I like the gay part.
有一个词？好吧，我喜欢同性恋的部分。
If anything, it could be more gay.
如果可以的话，它可以更同性恋一点。
You should gay it up,
你应该让它更同性恋一点，
and then, I like the "proud" part.
而且，我喜欢那“自豪”的部分。
(gulps) It's just the...
（吞口水）就是……
Christian part.
基督徒的部分。
Look, Richard, this is great,
听着，Richard，这是很好的，
because now I can be gay and a Christian.
因为现在我可以同时做一个同性恋和一个基督徒。
Or just be gay!
或者仅仅做一个同性恋!
You know, you could be a-- a twink.
你懂得，你可以做一个——一个twink（一种男性化的gay）
A bear, an otter.
（以下所说的统统是gay的类型）熊型，水濑型，
A circuit queen, a chub, a pup.
马戏团皇后，白鲑，小狗。
A gipster, a daddy chaser,
时髦型，恋父型，
a leatherman, a lady boy.
皮衣男，易性男孩。
You could be a Donald Duck,
你还能是唐老鸭
which is a gay guy who got kicked out of the Navy.
就那个被海军开除的基佬
Yeah, I-- I know what it is.
嗯，我~ 那个我知道
How do you know so many gay things?
你怎么那么懂基佬的事情啊？
I worked with a guy.
跟我共事的那家伙~
Just...
你就
don't be a Christian.
别当自己是个基督徒
(scoffs) Wow.
哇
After all you put me through,
怎么说你也让我度过了难关，
it turns out, you're biased too.
我这才发觉，你也是有偏见的。
No! No, no, no! I'm not!
不！不，不，没有，我没有！
I swear to you I'm not. I'm chill AF.
我向你发誓我没偏见。我可是很他妈的没偏见的。（AF：as fuck）
It's just everybody else.
只是别人都有。
Look, if you go Christian, I lose K-Hole games.
看，假如你公开自己是基督徒，我就会丢掉K-洞游戏了。
I cannot let that happen. I know it sucks.
我不能让事情变成那样。 我知道那很糟糕。
It's shitty, but it's the truth.
屎一样糟，但现实就是如此。
I'm gonna make things easy for you, Richard.
那我也不为难你了，Richard
I'm out.
我出了
Of the closet? No!
出柜？不！
The new Internet!
退出你这新互联网
The Internet you said was gonna be-- What was it?
你说过这新互联网将会是~ 是什么来着？
"The first truly free and open Internet."
“第一个真正自由并开放的互联网。”
Open for everyone.
对所有人都开放。
Whatever happened to that, huh?
这原则怎么没了，哈？
♪ ♪
Nice place.
环境不错嘛
Oh, thanks, yeah.
哦，谢谢，嗯
Oh, wow! That's a nice touch.
噢，哇！这摆设真不错
Big Head: Yeah, thanks!
嗯，谢谢！
The Monterey Bay Aquarium was testing their sonar,
蒙特雷湾水族馆在测试他们的声纳的时候，
and found this thing, like, two miles under the ocean.
发现了这东西，好像是，在海底两英里处。
And I figure, Erlich and I already bought it,
并且我想，我跟 Erlich 已经买下它了
so I might as well hold onto it.
所以我还是留着它吧
Plus, it weighs like 8,000 pounds,
再说，它都有 8 千榜那么重，
so I couldn't move it if I wanted to.
就算我想搬走它都不好搬
Well, and it also kinda works as your mascot.
嗯，它也可以作为你的吉祥物。
Right? 'Cause of your name?
对吧？因为你的名字
Oh, yeah, 'cause "Nelson."
哦，嗯，你是指 "Nelson.
Oh, I meant because it's a big head.
哦，我意思是说那个是大头
I guess that works, too.
我猜那也对。
So, what's up, man?
那么，你干嘛来啊，兄弟？
Um, well, I wanted to ask you--
嗯~ 我想问下你~
Oh! Big Head!
噢！大头啊！
(chuckles) Now I get it.
现在我明白你刚才的意思了
Sorry. Is-- is it possible
不好意思，有，有没有可能
that the general partnership that you formed with Erlich
你跟 Erlich 建立的合作关系
is still in effect?
是不是仍然有效？
Oh. No way.
噢，不可能。
You definitely dissolved it?
你确定已经解除了？
Yeah, my dad insisted.
是的，我爸爸坚持要那样
I remember he filled out this whole form for me,
我记得他为我填满了整个表格
and made me sign it,
还让我签字
mail it in and everything.
寄出去了搞好了一切
Yeah, 'cause I-- I remember I had the paperwork in one hand,
是的，因为我，我记得我一只手里拿着那份文件，
and the menu for Mr. Chow's in the other.
而另一只手拿着周先生的菜单。
And then--
然后--
(papers rustling)
（纸张的沙沙声）
♪ ♪
Oh, no way!
噢，不是吧！
Still have the paperwork.
那文件还在这里。
Guess I must have sent the menu.
我想我肯定是把菜单寄出去了
Big Head, this is great news.
大头，这是个天大的好消息啊
Scott: Gavin?
I think you're really going to love the changes
我想你会真正爱上这改变的
that my team has made to the presentation.
那是我的团队为展示会所做的。
I think you might like ours even better.
我想你会更喜欢我们的。
Sorry, what changes?
对不起，是什么改变来着？
We are presenting two paths,
我们现在有两种展示的方式，
and you alone will decide which one we walk, Gavin.
你来决定我们将用哪种，Gavin
What the fuck are you talking about?
你们操他妈的在讲什么啊？
I thought the presentation was fine as it is.
我觉得那展示会那样子就很好啊。
Wait. What? You did?
等等。什么？你这么认为？
Goddammit!
该死的！
Why is this still here?
为什么这个还在这儿？
I said it was too sticky.
我说过了这个太粘糊了。
Don't you listen to anything I say?
你们有听进去我说的任何话吗？
(sets bear down)
（放下小熊瓶子）
The bear... Sticky with honey.
那小熊瓶子……粘了蜂蜜黏黏的。
So what did you change?
那么你们改了什么？
Uh, the spotlight.
呃，聚光灯。
Yes! We're making it wider just like you asked.
是的！我们把它扩大了，就像你要求的。
Good.
好。
You know what? Let's show you to your dressing room. Yeah.
那什么，让我们带你去看看你的更衣室吧。是的。
And whenever you're ready, you let us know,
只要你准备好了，你就告诉我们，
we'll show you that spotlight, huh?
我们将会让你看一下那聚光灯，好吧？
- You're gonna love it.
- Sarah: We did it!
- 你将会非常喜欢的。
- Sarah: 我们做成了！
We had to fly him in from Tucson, but we got the bear.
我们不得不把它从图森市空运过来，终于搞到那熊了。
(bear growling)
（熊咆哮）
Gavin hates the bear. You failed!
Gavin讨厌那熊。你失败了！
Put everything back the way it was.
把所有的东西都放回去。
And widen the spotlight!
还有把聚光灯扩大一点！
Guess what, asshole.
你知道吗，混蛋。
Leon told me he wanted your ticket,
Leon告诉我你要你的那张票，
'cause he wants to go see BattleBots with me.
因为他想和我去看机器人格斗。
But then he remembered he actually had plans that night
但他想起来他那晚上另有计划
with a bunch of people, doesn't know what they're doing,
和一群人，不知道他们要干什么，
their plans are sort of fluid,
他们的计划是比较灵活的，
plus, it's like friends from his old work,
另外，那些是他旧工作里的朋友，
so it'd be weird if I hung out with them.
所以和他们一起玩会让我感觉挺怪的。
Anyway...
不管怎样…
looks like you and I are going to see BattleBots.
看起来你和我要去看机器人格斗了。
You're going to hang out with me,
你要和我一起了，
and have fun, whether you like it or not.
玩得开心点吧，不管你喜不喜欢。
And what goes best with BattleBots?
而和机器人格斗最好的搭配是什么？
That's right. Chicken wings.
没错。鸡翅膀。
That's why you get a sweet $50 gift card to Dave & Buster's.
这就是为什么让你拿一张50美元的礼品卡去Dave & Buster餐馆买。
Serves you right for fucking us over.
这是对你给我们捣乱的最好的惩罚。
Wash your fucking hair.
洗洗你的头发。
And you know what happens when I get drunk, Jeff?
然后你知道当我喝醉的时候会发生什么吗，Jeff？
I get so sincere.
我会非常真诚。
It's really awkward.
真的是很尴尬。
Fuck you, Jeff.
操你啊，Jeff.
Oh, um, can you drive?
哦，嗯，你开车行吗？
♪ ♪
Well, I spoke to La Flamme,
好的，我和La Flamme谈过了，
and it's official.
那时正式的了。
Big Head is still legally Erlich's next of kin.
大头是Erlich法定的继承人。
So Jian-Yang's whole gambit was for naught.
所以简阳所有的把戏都落空了。
Wow, really?
哇呜，真的吗？
Big Head owns Erlich's house, and 10% of Pied Piper.
大头拥有Erlich的房子，和花笛手10%的股份。
I called the sheriff and started eviction proceedings.
我打了电话给警长并开始了驱逐行动。
We're gonna get everything back.
我们将把所有东西收回来。
Oh, also, the, uh, OctoPipers are arriving for the meeting.
噢，还有，那个，嗯，八笛手们过来开会了。
It's a good thing that FirstSight dropped out, right?
“第一眼”退出是个好事，对吧？
'Cause we're back down to eight developers,
因为我们又回到了8个开发者，
so you can keep that name.
所以你可以保持用那个名字。
Actually, uh, no, we can't.
事实上，嗯，不，我们不能。
Wait, what?
等等，什么？
I'm glad this worked out. Yeah.
我很高兴这事能做成。   是的。
Thanks for dropping FirstSight.
谢谢把“第一眼”踢掉。
Jesus, my board would have nailed me to a cross.
耶稣啊，不然的话我的董事会会把我钉上十字架的。
Well, I think we're just about ready to get going here, uh...
嗯，我想我们正准备从这里开始，呃……
Oh. Hey!
哦。嘿！
Oh, good, there he is. What's he doing here?
哦，好，他来了。    他来干啥？
He is here because I asked him to be.
他来这儿是因为我叫他来的。
I want him to be one of our developers.
我想要他成为我们的开发者之一。
What? No! Fuck that guy!
什么？不！去他的！
Hey, man, how's it goin'?
嗨，各位，还好吗？
Richard. Deedee.
(whispers) Can I talk to you? Yeah!
（小声说）我能和你谈谈吗？   可以！
No, no, no. Actually, look!
不，不，不。事实上，看！
Look, guys, I...
看，伙计们，我…
I asked you to be a part of this
我请你们参与到这个来
because I thought you were willing to take a chance
因为我想你们愿意给个机会
on my idea.
给我的理想。
An entirely new Internet.
一个全新的互联网。
An Internet that is everything
这样一个互联网，它的所有一切
the old Internet is supposed to be, but isn't.
都应该是那个旧的互联网所应该实现的，但没有。
Truly free and truly open.
真实的自由，真正的开放。
Well, I'm sorry, gang.
哦，抱歉，伙伴们。
Truly open means "open to everyone."
真正的开放意味着“对每个人开放”。
No matter how repugnant their views are.
无论他们的观点是多么的不同。
How ignorant or stupid,
多么的无知或愚蠢，
or, to be honest, totally fucking wrong.
或者直接说，全他妈是错的。
And, look, who are we to judge, right?
而且，看看，我们有什么资格去评判呢，对吧？
There's some people out there that believe
有那么些人相信
that we're living in a computer simulation.
我们是生活在一个电脑虚拟世界里。
Well, that is supported by the evidence.
嗯，那是有证据支持的。
What?
什么？
Uh, it's basic probability theory.
额，那是基本的概率理论。
Right, uh, Richard, can I talk to you for just a sec? Yes, of course.
对，额，Richard，我先能和你谈谈一小会儿吗？     当然可以。
Uh, that's bullshit actually.
额，那实际上是瞎扯。
It's been disproven.
已经被证明是假的。
But why does that even matter?
但是那有什么关系吗？
In a few years, we'll all be working for robots.
在几年之后，我们将都为机器人工作。
No, that's stupid.
不，这想法太傻了。
The robots will be working for us.
机器人将为我们工作。
Robots? Who gives a fuck about robots?
机器人？谁他妈在乎机器人啊？
It's the artificial super intelligence we should be worried about.
我们应该担心的是人工智能。
Exactly, and that's why we have to stop it.
确实，这就是我们为什么得停掉（人工智能）。
Stop it? No, that's the us I'm talking about.
停掉它？不，那正是我所说的我们。
We have to bring it into existence.
我们要让它成为现实。
Otherwise, it'll find out who didn't believe in it, and punish them.
否则，它会查明谁不相信它，然后惩罚他们。
Clark: Right. Guys, I was wrong.
Clark：好吧。伙计们，我错了。
Um, Deedee is...
额，Deedee将...
not in. He's actually very much out.
不加入。他事实上非常彻底的出局了。
So...
所以...
do-over on the whole speech.
重新来个演讲吧。
Fuck that guy!
操他妈的！
Christians suck!
基督徒们真差劲！
And, uh, here's a good side effect though.
而且，额，这也有好的一面。
Uh, we all get to keep the name OctoPipers.
嗯，我们都将会保持叫八笛手这个名字。
You know what? Why don't we just take a quick five?
你们知道吗？为什么我们不休息五分钟呢？
(clears throat) And then, we'll BRB,
（清喉咙）然后，我们将很快回来。
and then, go teams.
再然后，加油！队友们！。
So just-- let's have a--
所以，让我们——
What just happened?
发生了什么？
Deedee's out?
Deedee退出了？
Yeah, well, he said
没错，好吧，他说
that right after he bailed on us,
就在他背弃我们之后，
he went out and made a deal with our competitor.
他去和我们的竞争者达成了协议。
But we don't have any competitors. Richard?
但是我们没有任何的竞争者啊，Richard？
Richard: Fuckin' Jian-Yang.
Richard：该死的简阳。
I'm gonna tear him a new asshole.
我要给他撕个新的屁眼出来。
It wasn't enough to do New Snapchat or New Expedia,
去做一个新的阅后即焚或一个新的亿客行还不够，
he had to do New Pied Piper too?
他还要做一个新的魔笛手？
Where did he get our code?
他怎么得到我们的代码的？
He was always stealing snacks from the office.
他一直都从办公室偷零食。
He could've lifted it from anywhere.
他可能从任何地方偷到。
I guess that's what happened to my lavender cheese.
我猜我的薰衣草奶酪就是这么没的。
(pounding on door) Richard: Jian-Yang! Open up!
（捶门）Richard: 简阳！开门！
Gilfoyle: What the fuck?
Gilfoyle: 他妈的怎么回事？
Why does every home I've ever loved get stripped?
为什么每一个我爱的家都会被偷光？
Is that Erlich in the bucket?
那是Erlich的骨灰桶吗？
♪ ♪
Uh... (clears throat)
呃……（清喉咙）
"Richard...
"Hello, I went to China to do new new Internet.
你好，我去中国做新的新互联网了。
"Thank you. Enjoy your house.
谢谢你。好好享受你的房子吧。
"I love you.
我爱你。
Jian-Yang."
简阳
(Chinese hip hop music playing)
（中国hip hop音乐播放）
I'm here with Pied Piper CEO Richard Hendricks,
（下集预告就不翻译了吧，给大家练练英语，哈哈）
and newly minted COO Jared Dunn.
Tell me what your new internet is,
and why Gavin Belson should be afraid of it.
-Manure? -INTERVIEWER: Pardon?
♪ (TECHNO MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
HOOVER: Sir, I had no idea they were this far along.
You must be furious.
That's the thing.
I'm not.
So, we're just giving a random company
a bunch of free compute power on our network?
Some company called Eklow.
BERTRAM GILFOYLE: The AI company?
Follow me, I'll introduce you to her.
Sorry-- Her?
Fiona.
-Good morning. -Isn't she pretty?
-♪ (MUSIC STOPS) ♪ -(ROBOT WHIRRING)
Yeah, sure. Yep.
♪ (MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪